Okay, so just a
quick update. What I
want you to do
right now is I
want you to go
over to Cynthia and
I want you to
write three things that
make you very credible
in this section. What
this is gonna do
is when you are
using guardrails to give
you feedback on your
introductions, it's gonna make
sure you inject some
credibility in. So I
need you to put
in three big brags,
three things that you
have achieved that your
viewers want to. Now
don't put something like,
I've got the Guinness
World Record for eating
a bucket load of
jelly. That's not an
achievement the viewers will
care about. It needs
to be credibility brags.
And then what I
want you to do
is I want you
to write your backstory.
So the storytelling module's
gonna help you more
with this, but all
I want you to
do is keep it
simple. Start with the
problem your viewer now
has that you solved,
talk about some actions
you took, and then
talk about the big
result it got. If
your backstory is not
relevant to your viewers,
let's say you're a
doctor who helps people
with bad backs and
you've never had a
back back, write the
backstory about the best
client result you've ever
got. And again, what's
gonna happen is when
you're using the AI
and guardrails to help
reposition your intros, it's
gonna bring in elements
of your backstory too.
That's it. On to
the next video.